(Sheldon:)Well, I should hope so.
Tomorrow's picture day.
(Penny:)Why are you
taking his side?
(Penny:)Because it's
important to him,
(Penny:)and when we signed the Roommate
Agreement, we made a deal.
Y-You keep talking like that,
you're gonna make color guard.
(video game sound effects
over TV)
(Raj:)Man, I'm worn out.
I know.
(Howard:)Imagine if we were
actually moving.
(Raj:)No, it's just, ever since I
started dating Claire and Emily
(Raj:)at the same time,
it's exhausting.
(Howard:)You're exhausted?
(Howard:)Try folding every five pages
in a pregnancy book
(Howard:)so your wife thinks you read it.
(Raj:)But, dude, you're so lucky.
(Raj:)Getting to stay home at night
with the woman you love.
(Howard:)I guess I am lucky.
(Raj:)You are, because
dating two women,
(Raj:)I mean, I can't even remember
(Raj:)the last time I slept
in my own apartment.
I wake up and I'm like, "Am I at
Claire's or am I at Emily's?
(Raj:)Is there a third girl
I've forgotten about?"
(Sheldon:)Like...
"Where am I?"